STEVEN SEMCO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

719-963-6450



stevensemcodev@gmail.com



https://stevensemco.com/

PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer based in the Denver/Colorado Springs metro areas. I am also an artist and muralist, that has multiple murals in the Colorado Springs and Manitou Springs areas. My passion for creation and creativity is a driving factor in both endeavors. My character, determination and work-ethic were forged from many years spent working the line of commercial kitchens.

EDUCATION

Pikes Peak Community College

AS in Computer Science 2020-Present

Ayden-Grifton High School

Graduate 2001-2005

SKILLS

Python

JavaScript

Django

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

React

Bootstrap

GitHub

HTML

CSS

Sass

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE TEACHING ASSISTANT

General Assembly | October 2021 - Present

- · Providing office hours support to current students in the SEI course at General Assembly.
- · Facilitating the learning process by guiding students towards solutions to ensure overall understanding.
- Helping students understand engineering concepts and processes.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE **FELLOW**

General Assembly | Summer 2021

- · Learned web development skills such as HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.
- Created applications using JavaScript and Python.
- Utilized libraries such as React, Django and Express, as well as database structures like MongoDB and SQL
- Crafted multiple large scale projects utilizing different development approaches.

KITCHEN MANAGER

Frankies Too | 2018 -2020

- · Enforcing restaurant policies and resolving staff concerns.
- · Food ordering, inventory and insuring food costs fall within a strict range.
- Training new staff and setting weekly schedules.
- · Cooking in a fast paced, high volume setting.
- Organizing meetings and following a vision for my team.